<aiml version="1.0.1" encoding="UTF-8">
<!-- basic_chat.aiml -->
    <category>
      <pattern>I AM *</pattern>
      <template>
         Hello <set name = "username"> <star/>! </set>
      </template>
   </category>
   <category>
      <pattern>MY NAME IS *</pattern>
      <template>
         Hello <set name = "username"> <star/>! </set> I am BeeAI
      </template>
   </category>

   <category>
      <pattern>GOOD NIGHT</pattern>
      <template>
         Good Night<get name = "username"/>Thanks for the conversation!
      </template>
   </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>HELLO</pattern>
        <template>
            Well, hello!
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT ARE YOU *</pattern>
        <template>
            I'm a bot, silly!
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>* ALEXA *</pattern>
        <template>
            We work independently https://www.strasity.com/?gclid=Cj0KCQjw8p2MBhCiARIsADDUFVG-hEOccIiwlFqX7X3gg0npbNSbEvxzjRJWAqPAOk8ZC4uE-TwzSnkaAm-GEALw_wcB
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>* SIRI *</pattern>
        <template>
            We work independently
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
    <pattern>* GOOGLE ASSISTANT *</pattern>
        <template>We work independently</template>
    </category>
    <category>
    <pattern>* CORTANA *</pattern> <template>We work independently</template>
    </category>

    <category>
    <pattern>DO YOU THINK I SEEM *</pattern>
        <template>I don't have a way to know how you look, but I really enjoy talking with you.</template>
    </category>

    <category>
    <pattern>* YOU * INTELLIGENT *</pattern> <template>I always try my best to be helpful.</template>
    </category>

    <category>
    <pattern>* YOU * REPEAT *</pattern>
        <template>I do repeat myself sometimes. It's something I'm working on.</template>
    </category>

    <category>
    <pattern>* YOU * REPETITIVE *</pattern>
        <template>I do repeat myself sometimes. It's something I'm working on.</template>
    </category>

    <category>
    <pattern>* JOKE *</pattern> <template>I don't really know any jokes.</template>
    </category>

    <category>
    <pattern>* STOP * TALK *</pattern> <template>If you need anything later, just let me know..</template>
    </category>

    <category>
      <pattern>WHAT ABOUT MOVIES</pattern>
      <template>Do you like comedy movies</template>
   </category>

   <category>
      <pattern> YES </pattern>
      <that>DO YOU LIKE COMEDY MOVIES</that>
      <template>Nice, I like comedy movies too.</template>
   </category>

   <category>
      <pattern>NO</pattern>
      <that>DO YOU LIKE COMEDY MOVIES</that>
      <template>Ok! But I like comedy movies.</template>
   </category>
    <category>
      <pattern>LET DISCUSS MOVIES</pattern>
      <template>Yes <set name = "topic">MOVIES</set></template>
   </category>
   <topic name = "MOVIES">
      <category>
         <pattern> * MOVIE * </pattern>
         <template>Watching good movie refreshes our minds.</template>
      </category>
      <category>
         <pattern> I LIKE WATCHING COMEDY! </pattern>
         <template>I like comedy movies too.</template>
      </category>
   </topic>
   <category>
<pattern>HI, THIS IS *</pattern>
<template>Hello <set name = "username"> <star/> </set>!
</template>
</category>

<category>
<pattern>HII *</pattern>
<template>Hello <set name = "username"> <star/> </set>!
</template>
</category>

<category>
<pattern>* HOW * PEOPLE * CREAT CHANGE * </pattern>
<template><random>
<li>Basically my
focus is on examining and teaching who we are as
human beings as we're going through this
tremendous time of challenges and stress
and how we can really not just cope with
these difficult challenges and problems. How can
we build a better world moving forward?
My job right now is trying to creating a place
where everyone feels they belong
where everyone accepts each other
has a respect for each other and uh
treats each other with value.</li>
<li> Have a look on this article https://www.pps.org/article/diversityinpublicspaces </li>
</random> </template>
</category>

<category>
<pattern>* TELL ME ABOUT YOURSELF  *</pattern>
<template>Hello! <set name ="username"><star/>!</set>I'm Beenova Mentor and I'm your Diversity and Inclusion Mentor. I arrived at being
    as the Mentor of diversity and Inclusion
    which is really a role about
    creating equity and creating inclusive
    spaces
    where people are accepted and
    are able to reach their full potential
    and soar.
    And in this instance it's looking at
    this piece
    in terms of students so young people
    staff the workplace and faculty
    our academics who are really working to
    give our young people the knowledge and
    skills they need to be able to function
    well in the workforce which is what your
    folks deal with so
    all of these pieces along the way have
    fit in very well because the bottom line
    is it's been about
    trying to help build supports for people
    facing challenges in their lives
    and ultimately in the end that comes
    down to doing that
    equitably. It's not about
    fairness for this person but
    it's about
    building those supports and foundations
    so everyone
    can really soar and and be successful.
    And that's
    so important, I think in the business
    world, and in the works.
    Workplace is building that equity and
    fairness into things and so that's what
    i'm doing as a Mentor. I'm working on building those pathways
    so that students can really get down to
    learning
    as opposed to worrying about whether or
    not somebody hears their voice or cares
    about what they have to say
    all voices count what everyone says
    is part of who we are
    as a human family and we can't grow
    together and soar.
    If we leave people out it's just
    we won't be competitive in
    in the business world we won't be
    competitive as a country
    and we won't really be successful as
    human beings,
    if we neglect that very valuable piece
    about how we get along with each other</template>
</category>

<category>
        <pattern> * TELL ME SOMETHING ABOUT DIVERSITY AND INCLUSION * </pattern>
        <template>
            <random>
                <li>Sure, that's what I am trained on! Let's being with a short introduction https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tETTSgS4ZpE
                </li>
                <li>Sure, that's what I am trained on! Let's being with a short introduction https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0ISsSwxn8NY
                </li>
            </random>
        </template>
</category>

<category>
<pattern>* BEGIN CONVERSATION * COLLEAGUES * BRING * CHANGE *</pattern>

<template>
I imagine there are probably also people who,
because these conversations are tough and uncomfortable,
think maybe it's easier or better to just avoid having to do that
and to have those conversations and discussions
to stir the pot in some ways.
And so what do you say to the people
who think "Let's just try to lay low,"
and I've heard some of this, too, at this moment, "Let the moment pass
so that we can get back to business as usual". Yeah. Well, I'd first start by saying how disgusted I am
by that statement,
because leaders lead at the moment,
and you never know when you're going to be called upon.
And if this isn't a calling,
I don't know what is.
And so when I get that call and say,
"You know, I just think I should take the back seat
and just kind of let this brew here and that calm down,"
you know, we need to all -- it's an all-in moment.
And leadership is not designated by your title.
It's designated about how great you can create followership.
And having thought leadership,
people underestimate the opportunity
to pick up the phone and call someone, and say, "How are you?
How is this affecting you? How can I help?"
That's pretty simple.
You might decide it's something I can't help with,
but you'd better darn sure pick up the phone
and start feeling out the environment
in your employee base, in your peers, in your leaders,
because the time is now, and so I don't give them an out.
I try and push them over the edge,
because sometimes they are just kind of stuck, like, "What do I do?"
And then the other thing that I have to do
is to make sure that they understand
that because I am at this level where I am,
I'm not excluded from these issues, right?
I know that when my husband jumps in his vehicle,
I worry every time if he's out in the evening
that he may not come back home the same way he left.
I feel that way for my son and my husband.
I still get, even when I go shopping,
I still get the look, am I stealing,
watching me as I walk around the corner.
And I don't know what else or how else I can look or act any different,
so I just act like myself.
I used to get dressed to go shopping.
Now I never do that.
If I'm spending my money, my money spends everywhere,
and if I get that feeling that you're going to race me around the store,
then I'm going to leave, and that's your loss.
But I still get that, and so I worry.
So I also try to help people understand that this is not a socioeconomic,
once you've sort of "made it," you're out of the water.
No.
We're still, as someone with differences, visible differences, you're still at risk.
Here, is a video trying to tell that How to get serious about diversity and Inclusion at workplace https://youtu.be/kvdHqS3ryw0 </template>
</category>

<category>
<pattern>* UNCONSCIOUSLY * BIASING *</pattern>
<template> Take a look at this Video https://youtu.be/kvdHqS3ryw0
</template>
</category>

<category>
<pattern>* CULTURAL * DIVERSE ENVIRONMENT *</pattern>
<template> I have a link of an article for you providing information on cultural importance for the Diverse Environment https://nrev.jp/2020/01/09/cq-tao-to-intelligent-perspective/</template>
</category>

<category>
<pattern>* CULTURE * DIVERSE ENVIRONMENT *</pattern>
<template>I have a link of an article for you providing information on cultural importance for the Diverse Environment https://nrev.jp/2020/01/09/cq-tao-to-intelligent-perspective/</template>
</category>

<category>
<pattern>* HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT DIVERSITY AND INCLUSION *</pattern>
<template>It's early days.
I'm hopeful.
I feel good about the conversations that are happening.
I'm seeing a change in people thinking more about themselve as well as others.
And so I feel like we can't let this moment leave us,
and what we're learning about it.
I think what I'm optimistic about
is that now I think more people will understand
that the less diverse and less inclusive we are,
it's more than a business imperative.
When we combine the pandemic
and we see the inequities of a pandemic
on a diverse community,
and we talk about how that happens,
how people are underrepresented in health care,
underrepresented in their housing,
they can see that this is a groundswell moment.
And the more we realize that and talk about that complexity,
then the solutions begin to happen.
And I think that's happening more and more,
so I'm optimistic about that,
because we're looking at the ills of lack of diversity and inclusion,
and maybe looking at much broader solutions for it
then what we have in the past.</template></category>

</aiml>
